I'm trying to lock on to every customer who comes to any meeting with the feeling that I won't miss them or let them go.
It's wonderful that you can use the word “lock on” properly.
I'm so awake that I walked my dog in the morning before coming here today.
Healthy is great.
I've had three patterns of scary dreams since I was a little girl.
Wait a minute, this is very interesting!
The kettle and the idol
Hi there, I'm Yakan.
I grew up in the old Stardust office.
Well then, let's get started.
I'd like to call today's guest.
This is our idol. Come in.
Hello! Lock on to your hearts!
I'm Aki Suda, a.k.a. Aki-chan as “Super Tokimeki Lemon,” from Cho Tokimeki Sendenbu.
We have Aki Suda from the Cho Tokimeki Sendenbu.
Thank you very much. Nice to meet you.
Please call me Aki.
This is a very difficult story.
I will do my best to finally call you after recording from here!
Did you know the title of this night?
Yes, of course.
I see that Kanami from the same group has also made an appearance.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you.
I'd like to get started right away.
I'd like to ask you a few questions about the Cho Tokimeki Sendenbu.
I was wondering if I could ask you a few questions.
Asato Pose
Thank you very much.
I'd like to come to you.
I understand that you were on a national tour this summer.
That's right.
It's over now.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
We performed 11 shows this time, including overseas performances.
I was able to go to Korea for the first time in my life.
I was able to go to Indonesia for the first time in the last year.
I was also able to go to various places in Japan where I performed for the first time.
It was a very memorable concert at every venue.
Did you feel at a loss when you were overseas because of the differences from your usual life in Japan?
Yes, but Korea is much closer to Japan.
But in Indonesia, there are many really friendly people.
Did you go to some places in Japan for the first time?
We went to Ibaraki for the first time and I had natto  and it was delicious. I'm sure you'll be able to find something you'd like to eat.
Pizza Paella is so delicious!
When I said I wanted to eat that or pizza, they immediately bought it for me.
It's a very selfish choice, but I really enjoyed the food from Pizza.
Pizza was delicious!
I see. Thank you very much.
Such a Cho Tokimeki Sendenbu, you know, is still buzzing with the Saijokyuuni Kawaii no,
Suda, do you feel that this song has become a buzzword?
Do you ever feel that it is popular?
But, you know, the other day, when I was walking around town, there was a girl in front of me dancing to the most popular song.
It's a little dangerous.
Is it really dangerous?
I was so happy to see a girl dancing to the song.
I was so happy.
You couldn't speak to her?
I did, but I also danced a little as I passed her.
I hope the people who were dancing noticed me.
I heard that you went down to the audience for fan service on the “Saijokyuuni Kawaiino” tour.
That's right.
We always have a “recording free time” where we are allowed to take pictures of the audience.
This time it was during the song.
I was a little nervous because it was the first time for me to try it.
I was a little bit nervous because it was the first time for me to try it.
Some of them said, “Wow!
I was so happy.
Is there anything you are conscious of when you give fan service?
Yes, but since they came all the way to the concert, I go far away from them.
I go to the back of the first floor, the second floor, the third floor, and so on,
I try to lock on to the audience on every floor with the feeling that I will never miss them or let them go.
It is wonderful that you can use the word “lock on” properly!
Isn't it difficult or tiring to go so far up the stairs?
I'm getting a little tired on the stairs.
But I know I can do my best to see everyone's smiling faces, so I do my best.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'll see you later.
I'm sure we'll have a lot to talk about in the future.
I'm sure we'll be hearing a lot more from you tomorrow onward.
Please do.
I can't even drink coffee yet.
I can drink it if it's sweetened, but coffee is already coffee.
So I see... this program is...
Bake-chan!
Darling
Kei.
Unidentified Hiro-kun
This program was provided by Ruhana
Thank you very much.